export const quizData = [
  { question: "29 - 30?", answer: "-1", options: ["-3", "-1", "0", "4"] },
  { question: "17 + 15?", answer: "32", options: ["27", "28", "32", "37"] },
  {
    question: "111 / 37?",
    answer: "3.0",
    options: ["1.0", "3.0", "6.0", "7.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "48 / 3?",
    answer: "16.0",
    options: ["12.0", "13.0", "14.0", "16.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "825 / 25?",
    answer: "33.0",
    options: ["31.0", "33.0", "36.0", "37.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "585 / 39?",
    answer: "15.0",
    options: ["10.0", "12.0", "14.0", "15.0"],
  },
  { question: "38 + 8?", answer: "46", options: ["41", "43", "44", "46"] },
  { question: "2 + 49?", answer: "51", options: ["50", "51", "53", "54"] },
  {
    question: "11 * 28?",
    answer: "308",
    options: ["303", "306", "307", "308"],
  },
  {
    question: "150 / 25?",
    answer: "6.0",
    options: ["5.0", "6.0", "7.0", "11.0"],
  },
  { question: "28 * 1?", answer: "28", options: ["25", "26", "28", "31"] },
  {
    question: "882 / 18?",
    answer: "49.0",
    options: ["45.0", "49.0", "50.0", "51.0"],
  },
  { question: "36 * 1?", answer: "36", options: ["31", "34", "36", "38"] },
  { question: "19 + 31?", answer: "50", options: ["50", "52", "53", "54"] },
  { question: "46 - 45?", answer: "1", options: ["-4", "-2", "1", "3"] },
  { question: "13 + 28?", answer: "41", options: ["37", "40", "41", "43"] },
  { question: "30 - 42?", answer: "-12", options: ["-17", "-13", "-12", "-9"] },
  {
    question: "513 / 27?",
    answer: "19.0",
    options: ["18.0", "19.0", "23.0", "24.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "966 / 46?",
    answer: "21.0",
    options: ["16.0", "17.0", "21.0", "24.0"],
  },
  { question: "35 - 49?", answer: "-14", options: ["-16", "-15", "-14", "-9"] },
  { question: "14 + 17?", answer: "31", options: ["29", "31", "32", "33"] },
  { question: "1 * 8?", answer: "8", options: ["5", "8", "9", "11"] },
  { question: "2 * 43?", answer: "86", options: ["84", "86", "87", "90"] },
  {
    question: "12 * 25?",
    answer: "300",
    options: ["298", "300", "304", "305"],
  },
  { question: "42 + 33?", answer: "75", options: ["71", "72", "75", "80"] },
  { question: "17 + 9?", answer: "26", options: ["23", "26", "27", "29"] },
  { question: "46 + 40?", answer: "86", options: ["83", "86", "88", "91"] },
  {
    question: "11 - 37?",
    answer: "-26",
    options: ["-30", "-28", "-26", "-22"],
  },
  { question: "12 + 14?", answer: "26", options: ["23", "24", "25", "26"] },
  { question: "7 - 19?", answer: "-12", options: ["-16", "-13", "-12", "-9"] },
  { question: "47 * 3?", answer: "141", options: ["140", "141", "143", "145"] },
  {
    question: "90 / 45?",
    answer: "2.0",
    options: ["-3.0", "-2.0", "1.0", "2.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "66 / 2?",
    answer: "33.0",
    options: ["30.0", "32.0", "33.0", "36.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "13 - 33?",
    answer: "-20",
    options: ["-23", "-20", "-18", "-16"],
  },
  { question: "9 / 3?", answer: "3.0", options: ["1.0", "3.0", "5.0", "6.0"] },
  {
    question: "16 / 16?",
    answer: "1.0",
    options: ["-1.0", "1.0", "2.0", "5.0"],
  },
  { question: "38 - 18?", answer: "20", options: ["18", "19", "20", "24"] },
  {
    question: "1920 / 40?",
    answer: "48.0",
    options: ["45.0", "48.0", "50.0", "52.0"],
  },
  { question: "23 + 30?", answer: "53", options: ["50", "53", "55", "56"] },
  { question: "30 - 40?", answer: "-10", options: ["-11", "-10", "-8", "-7"] },
  { question: "24 + 3?", answer: "27", options: ["27", "28", "29", "30"] },
  {
    question: "48 * 45?",
    answer: "2160",
    options: ["2156", "2158", "2159", "2160"],
  },
  {
    question: "25 * 46?",
    answer: "1150",
    options: ["1148", "1150", "1152", "1153"],
  },
  {
    question: "1482 / 39?",
    answer: "38.0",
    options: ["35.0", "38.0", "41.0", "43.0"],
  },
  { question: "12 + 19?", answer: "31", options: ["26", "31", "32", "35"] },
  {
    question: "31 * 35?",
    answer: "1085",
    options: ["1082", "1085", "1087", "1089"],
  },
  {
    question: "19 * 22?",
    answer: "418",
    options: ["415", "418", "422", "423"],
  },
  { question: "48 - 25?", answer: "23", options: ["18", "23", "25", "26"] },
  { question: "14 - 5?", answer: "9", options: ["8", "9", "13", "14"] },
  { question: "22 + 33?", answer: "55", options: ["52", "53", "54", "55"] },
  {
    question: "21 - 35?",
    answer: "-14",
    options: ["-19", "-18", "-14", "-13"],
  },
  {
    question: "480 / 15?",
    answer: "32.0",
    options: ["28.0", "32.0", "34.0", "36.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "714 / 17?",
    answer: "42.0",
    options: ["39.0", "41.0", "42.0", "43.0"],
  },
  { question: "18 + 32?", answer: "50", options: ["48", "50", "52", "53"] },
  {
    question: "720 / 18?",
    answer: "40.0",
    options: ["36.0", "38.0", "40.0", "42.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "22 / 1?",
    answer: "22.0",
    options: ["17.0", "22.0", "25.0", "26.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "1248 / 26?",
    answer: "48.0",
    options: ["44.0", "46.0", "47.0", "48.0"],
  },
  { question: "19 * 1?", answer: "19", options: ["17", "19", "22", "24"] },
  {
    question: "1462 / 43?",
    answer: "34.0",
    options: ["29.0", "33.0", "34.0", "36.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "392 / 8?",
    answer: "49.0",
    options: ["49.0", "51.0", "52.0", "54.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "18 * 31?",
    answer: "558",
    options: ["554", "558", "559", "560"],
  },
  { question: "5 * 18?", answer: "90", options: ["85", "86", "90", "93"] },
  { question: "50 * 9?", answer: "450", options: ["446", "448", "450", "453"] },
  {
    question: "24 * 11?",
    answer: "264",
    options: ["260", "262", "263", "264"],
  },
  { question: "36 - 26?", answer: "10", options: ["6", "7", "10", "12"] },
  { question: "49 - 28?", answer: "21", options: ["20", "21", "23", "25"] },
  {
    question: "49 * 13?",
    answer: "637",
    options: ["632", "635", "637", "639"],
  },
  {
    question: "931 / 49?",
    answer: "19.0",
    options: ["15.0", "18.0", "19.0", "21.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "875 / 25?",
    answer: "35.0",
    options: ["30.0", "32.0", "35.0", "39.0"],
  },
  { question: "48 - 9?", answer: "39", options: ["36", "37", "38", "39"] },
  { question: "31 - 17?", answer: "14", options: ["13", "14", "15", "18"] },
  { question: "49 + 34?", answer: "83", options: ["78", "82", "83", "84"] },
  {
    question: "240 / 24?",
    answer: "10.0",
    options: ["6.0", "9.0", "10.0", "12.0"],
  },
  { question: "15 - 13?", answer: "2", options: ["1", "2", "6", "7"] },
  {
    question: "416 / 13?",
    answer: "32.0",
    options: ["30.0", "32.0", "33.0", "34.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "84 / 42?",
    answer: "2.0",
    options: ["1.0", "2.0", "3.0", "4.0"],
  },
  { question: "27 + 20?", answer: "47", options: ["44", "45", "47", "52"] },
  {
    question: "19 * 12?",
    answer: "228",
    options: ["224", "228", "231", "232"],
  },
  {
    question: "28 * 19?",
    answer: "532",
    options: ["531", "532", "536", "537"],
  },
  { question: "43 - 25?", answer: "18", options: ["15", "18", "20", "22"] },
  { question: "41 * 5?", answer: "205", options: ["203", "204", "205", "206"] },
  { question: "23 - 13?", answer: "10", options: ["7", "9", "10", "11"] },
  {
    question: "10 * 26?",
    answer: "260",
    options: ["256", "257", "260", "262"],
  },
  {
    question: "77 / 11?",
    answer: "7.0",
    options: ["6.0", "7.0", "8.0", "10.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "174 / 29?",
    answer: "6.0",
    options: ["5.0", "6.0", "8.0", "9.0"],
  },
  { question: "40 - 9?", answer: "31", options: ["29", "30", "31", "35"] },
  {
    question: "14 * 27?",
    answer: "378",
    options: ["376", "377", "378", "382"],
  },
  {
    question: "50 * 18?",
    answer: "900",
    options: ["895", "900", "902", "904"],
  },
  { question: "7 - 33?", answer: "-26", options: ["-31", "-26", "-25", "-23"] },
  { question: "44 - 14?", answer: "30", options: ["25", "26", "27", "30"] },
  {
    question: "21 * 23?",
    answer: "483",
    options: ["480", "483", "486", "487"],
  },
  { question: "2 * 11?", answer: "22", options: ["19", "22", "23", "26"] },
  {
    question: "34 * 47?",
    answer: "1598",
    options: ["1598", "1599", "1601", "1603"],
  },
  { question: "41 - 15?", answer: "26", options: ["22", "26", "28", "31"] },
  { question: "43 - 6?", answer: "37", options: ["35", "37", "40", "42"] },
  {
    question: "46 / 23?",
    answer: "2.0",
    options: ["-2.0", "0.0", "2.0", "4.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "658 / 47?",
    answer: "14.0",
    options: ["12.0", "13.0", "14.0", "17.0"],
  },
  { question: "45 + 29?", answer: "74", options: ["72", "74", "78", "79"] },
  {
    question: "630 / 30?",
    answer: "21.0",
    options: ["18.0", "21.0", "23.0", "26.0"],
  },
  { question: "25 - 10?", answer: "15", options: ["14", "15", "16", "17"] },
  {
    question: "41 * 35?",
    answer: "1435",
    options: ["1430", "1434", "1435", "1437"],
  },
  {
    question: "38 * 12?",
    answer: "456",
    options: ["451", "456", "457", "461"],
  },
  { question: "24 + 40?", answer: "64", options: ["64", "65", "66", "68"] },
  { question: "1 + 28?", answer: "29", options: ["27", "28", "29", "34"] },
  {
    question: "242 / 11?",
    answer: "22.0",
    options: ["20.0", "21.0", "22.0", "27.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "12 - 28?",
    answer: "-16",
    options: ["-18", "-16", "-15", "-14"],
  },
  {
    question: "46 * 49?",
    answer: "2254",
    options: ["2252", "2253", "2254", "2258"],
  },
  { question: "40 + 40?", answer: "80", options: ["76", "78", "80", "82"] },
  {
    question: "225 / 9?",
    answer: "25.0",
    options: ["21.0", "23.0", "25.0", "30.0"],
  },
  { question: "14 * 2?", answer: "28", options: ["23", "25", "26", "28"] },
  {
    question: "96 / 3?",
    answer: "32.0",
    options: ["27.0", "30.0", "32.0", "35.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "46 * 45?",
    answer: "2070",
    options: ["2067", "2070", "2071", "2072"],
  },
  { question: "8 * 12?", answer: "96", options: ["94", "96", "97", "98"] },
  {
    question: "38 * 10?",
    answer: "380",
    options: ["379", "380", "381", "383"],
  },
  { question: "44 + 24?", answer: "68", options: ["66", "68", "69", "71"] },
  { question: "28 + 5?", answer: "33", options: ["33", "34", "35", "36"] },
  {
    question: "46 * 41?",
    answer: "1886",
    options: ["1883", "1886", "1887", "1889"],
  },
  { question: "22 - 24?", answer: "-2", options: ["-5", "-2", "-1", "1"] },
  { question: "34 - 15?", answer: "19", options: ["14", "18", "19", "23"] },
  { question: "30 - 39?", answer: "-9", options: ["-13", "-9", "-6", "-4"] },
  { question: "3 + 6?", answer: "9", options: ["5", "6", "9", "12"] },
  { question: "35 + 49?", answer: "84", options: ["79", "81", "83", "84"] },
  { question: "7 - 11?", answer: "-4", options: ["-5", "-4", "-2", "0"] },
  { question: "15 + 23?", answer: "38", options: ["36", "37", "38", "43"] },
  { question: "12 + 20?", answer: "32", options: ["28", "31", "32", "34"] },
  {
    question: "12 * 17?",
    answer: "204",
    options: ["204", "205", "206", "207"],
  },
  { question: "49 * 3?", answer: "147", options: ["142", "145", "147", "151"] },
  { question: "29 + 31?", answer: "60", options: ["58", "60", "61", "63"] },
  {
    question: "624 / 26?",
    answer: "24.0",
    options: ["19.0", "20.0", "22.0", "24.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "1800 / 40?",
    answer: "45.0",
    options: ["41.0", "42.0", "43.0", "45.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "27 * 32?",
    answer: "864",
    options: ["860", "863", "864", "865"],
  },
  {
    question: "2208 / 46?",
    answer: "48.0",
    options: ["46.0", "48.0", "50.0", "51.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "12 * 39?",
    answer: "468",
    options: ["463", "466", "467", "468"],
  },
  {
    question: "220 / 44?",
    answer: "5.0",
    options: ["3.0", "4.0", "5.0", "10.0"],
  },
  { question: "10 - 9?", answer: "1", options: ["-4", "1", "2", "5"] },
  { question: "8 + 49?", answer: "57", options: ["53", "57", "58", "60"] },
  {
    question: "48 * 28?",
    answer: "1344",
    options: ["1340", "1342", "1344", "1347"],
  },
  { question: "3 + 26?", answer: "29", options: ["27", "29", "30", "34"] },
  { question: "48 - 7?", answer: "41", options: ["39", "41", "42", "46"] },
  { question: "27 + 18?", answer: "45", options: ["41", "43", "45", "47"] },
  {
    question: "43 * 23?",
    answer: "989",
    options: ["989", "990", "991", "992"],
  },
  { question: "5 + 48?", answer: "53", options: ["50", "51", "53", "55"] },
  {
    question: "56 / 2?",
    answer: "28.0",
    options: ["26.0", "28.0", "29.0", "31.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "40 * 11?",
    answer: "440",
    options: ["438", "440", "442", "445"],
  },
  {
    question: "12 * 29?",
    answer: "348",
    options: ["343", "346", "348", "353"],
  },
  {
    question: "176 / 8?",
    answer: "22.0",
    options: ["19.0", "22.0", "23.0", "26.0"],
  },
  { question: "35 * 3?", answer: "105", options: ["100", "104", "105", "106"] },
  { question: "1 - 13?", answer: "-12", options: ["-17", "-16", "-12", "-10"] },
  { question: "25 * 6?", answer: "150", options: ["148", "150", "151", "153"] },
  {
    question: "329 / 7?",
    answer: "47.0",
    options: ["46.0", "47.0", "48.0", "50.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "19 * 18?",
    answer: "342",
    options: ["342", "344", "345", "347"],
  },
  { question: "37 - 4?", answer: "33", options: ["31", "33", "35", "38"] },
  { question: "8 - 14?", answer: "-6", options: ["-9", "-6", "-4", "-2"] },
  {
    question: "15 - 43?",
    answer: "-28",
    options: ["-31", "-28", "-26", "-23"],
  },
  { question: "7 * 27?", answer: "189", options: ["187", "188", "189", "191"] },
  {
    question: "27 - 47?",
    answer: "-20",
    options: ["-24", "-22", "-20", "-19"],
  },
  {
    question: "285 / 15?",
    answer: "19.0",
    options: ["15.0", "19.0", "22.0", "23.0"],
  },
  { question: "16 + 27?", answer: "43", options: ["42", "43", "44", "46"] },
  {
    question: "10 * 17?",
    answer: "170",
    options: ["165", "166", "167", "170"],
  },
  { question: "49 - 9?", answer: "40", options: ["38", "39", "40", "43"] },
  { question: "17 - 15?", answer: "2", options: ["-2", "2", "4", "6"] },
  {
    question: "248 / 31?",
    answer: "8.0",
    options: ["4.0", "8.0", "12.0", "13.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "874 / 23?",
    answer: "38.0",
    options: ["36.0", "38.0", "40.0", "41.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "28 * 19?",
    answer: "532",
    options: ["532", "533", "534", "536"],
  },
  {
    question: "31 * 42?",
    answer: "1302",
    options: ["1299", "1301", "1302", "1305"],
  },
  {
    question: "608 / 32?",
    answer: "19.0",
    options: ["17.0", "19.0", "21.0", "24.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "425 / 17?",
    answer: "25.0",
    options: ["23.0", "24.0", "25.0", "27.0"],
  },
  { question: "23 + 17?", answer: "40", options: ["36", "40", "43", "45"] },
  { question: "3 * 50?", answer: "150", options: ["148", "150", "153", "155"] },
  { question: "32 - 10?", answer: "22", options: ["21", "22", "24", "27"] },
  {
    question: "648 / 18?",
    answer: "36.0",
    options: ["32.0", "36.0", "37.0", "41.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "392 / 14?",
    answer: "28.0",
    options: ["23.0", "26.0", "28.0", "33.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "1110 / 30?",
    answer: "37.0",
    options: ["36.0", "37.0", "39.0", "40.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "135 / 45?",
    answer: "3.0",
    options: ["-1.0", "1.0", "3.0", "7.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "46 * 44?",
    answer: "2024",
    options: ["2024", "2025", "2027", "2029"],
  },
  {
    question: "1056 / 24?",
    answer: "44.0",
    options: ["41.0", "44.0", "45.0", "46.0"],
  },
  { question: "40 + 35?", answer: "75", options: ["70", "73", "75", "77"] },
  { question: "35 + 3?", answer: "38", options: ["33", "38", "39", "40"] },
  {
    question: "12 - 34?",
    answer: "-22",
    options: ["-25", "-22", "-19", "-18"],
  },
  {
    question: "36 * 42?",
    answer: "1512",
    options: ["1508", "1511", "1512", "1516"],
  },
  { question: "3 * 50?", answer: "150", options: ["146", "150", "152", "154"] },
  {
    question: "228 / 19?",
    answer: "12.0",
    options: ["7.0", "12.0", "14.0", "16.0"],
  },
  { question: "46 - 37?", answer: "9", options: ["4", "6", "8", "9"] },
  { question: "42 + 15?", answer: "57", options: ["52", "56", "57", "58"] },
  { question: "1 + 11?", answer: "12", options: ["9", "12", "15", "16"] },
  {
    question: "16 / 1?",
    answer: "16.0",
    options: ["14.0", "16.0", "19.0", "20.0"],
  },
  { question: "6 - 21?", answer: "-15", options: ["-19", "-16", "-15", "-13"] },
  { question: "3 - 1?", answer: "2", options: ["-1", "2", "4", "6"] },
  {
    question: "41 * 21?",
    answer: "861",
    options: ["856", "857", "861", "863"],
  },
  { question: "47 - 17?", answer: "30", options: ["28", "29", "30", "34"] },
  {
    question: "410 / 41?",
    answer: "10.0",
    options: ["8.0", "9.0", "10.0", "11.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "900 / 18?",
    answer: "50.0",
    options: ["45.0", "50.0", "52.0", "54.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "117 / 13?",
    answer: "9.0",
    options: ["6.0", "7.0", "9.0", "11.0"],
  },
  { question: "45 + 17?", answer: "62", options: ["57", "62", "66", "67"] },
  { question: "12 + 27?", answer: "39", options: ["37", "39", "41", "44"] },
  {
    question: "175 / 7?",
    answer: "25.0",
    options: ["21.0", "24.0", "25.0", "27.0"],
  },
  {
    question: "29 / 29?",
    answer: "1.0",
    options: ["-1.0", "0.0", "1.0", "5.0"],
  },
  { question: "22 - 7?", answer: "15", options: ["11", "15", "16", "18"] },
  { question: "26 + 41?", answer: "67", options: ["66", "67", "69", "72"] },
  { question: "7 * 12?", answer: "84", options: ["83", "84", "86", "89"] },
];
